Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1940-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Harper, Shirley
/4169
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3108934
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 13, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4108: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Librarian's Office.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
3108934
- Reports and Stats (1975/6- 1984/5), 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reports and Stats (1965/6 - 1974/5), 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Reports and Stats (1955/6 - 1964/5), 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Library, Nyssilr - General (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Library, Nyssilr C-1 General (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Nyssilr, General - C-1.7 Library Letter (Box 1, Folder 6)
- C-7.1 - Library Reports, Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 7)
- C-7.12 - Library Reports, Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 8)
- C-7.5-4 - Unit Reports, Annual Reports (State Universities) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Budget - Monthly Expenditure Reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Nyssilr, Library - Monthly Budget Report (CUL), April 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Nyssilr, Library - C-7.5 Unit Reports, Librarian's Office (1968) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ILR Catherwood Library - History (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Library History (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Lib, Ping (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Status and Needs - Summer 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Current Documents (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Long Range Plan (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Empire State - G. Horton (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Baruch (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Asst. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Air Cond. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 3-year Plans (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ILR Library - Planning (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ILR Library Planning (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NYSSILR - Proposal Five-Year Plan for Documentation Program (1974/5 - 1979/80), 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Five Year Plans - Planning (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ILR Library Planning (1975-1980) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ILR Library - Five Year Plans (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Five Year Plan Draft - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- ILR Library (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Files Office Report (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Martin P. Catherwood Library - Statistics (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Sample Memos, etc. (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Reports and Stats. (1945/6 - 1954/5), 1945-1955 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- ILR Library - Staff Meetings (Box 1, Folder 36)
- ILR Library - General Administration (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Organization Charts, etc. (Box 1, Folder 38)
- NYSSILR Library - Traffic Count and Room Attendance, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Report on Library Services for NYSSILR, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- NYSSILR Library Regulations (Box 1, Folder 41)
- NYSSILR Library Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 42)
- NYSSILR Library - Evaluation of State Programs (1959-1960) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- NYSSILR Library - Special Reports (Box 1, Folder 44)
- NYSSILR Library Special Reports - Proposed Program, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- NYSSILR Library Special Reports - Proposed Program, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- NYSSILR Library Special Reports, Proposed Program 1948 (copy 3) (Box 1, Folder 47)
- NYSSILR Library - Annual Reports (Extra Copies) (Box 1, Folder 48)
- ILR Library Statistics, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- ACQN (Box 2, Folder 1)
- CAT (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILR/Olin Conser (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ILR Library Technical Provisions (Cost Data) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR Library Technical Processors (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cost of CAT for ILR (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CAT Charges - 1977 Study (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Cataloguing Charges (Box 2, Folder 8)
- LMDC Brochures (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Mgmt/Pers. Archives (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NY Perb. (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Frank Columbus (Box 2, Folder 12)
- RR Collections (Box 2, Folder 13)
- ILR Library - LMDC (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Archives Sub-Committee (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Special LMDC Collections (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Oral History and UTY (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Cornell University General (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Intra-University Memoranda (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Cornell University - Purchasing Department (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Cornell University Parking Policy (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Cornell University Libraries - Library Handbook & Policy (Box 2, Folder 22)
- CUL Procedures (Previous) (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Library Acquisitions, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- CUL Bulletin - November 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Cornell University (Martin) - Director of the Libraries (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Acquisitions - CUL Special Project and Funds (Box 2, Folder 27)
- AII-40 Interlibrary Service (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Cornell University Libraries - Special Report - Card Catalogs (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Cornell University Libraries - Misc. Reports (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Other Campus Libraries - College of Agriculture Library (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Other Campus Libraries - Annex Library (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Other Campus Libraries - School of Business and Public Administration (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Other Campus Libraries - College of Engineering (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Other Campus Libraries - Law Library (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Other Campus Libraries - College of Veterinary Medicine (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Cornell Library News, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- State University Memoranda (Box 3, Folder 1)
- State University Newsletters (Box 3, Folder 2)
- State Library/Education Department (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NY and National Conference on Libraries (Box 3, Folder 4)
- SUNY 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- SUNY Council 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SUNY Council Board (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Headlines 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- SUNY Council (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SUNY Council 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- SUNY (Box 3, Folder 11)
- SUNY Council - April 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- SUNY Council of Head Librarians (Box 3, Folder 13)
- ILR Library - SUNY "Open Access" (Box 3, Folder 14)
- ILR Library - SUNY Projects and Programs (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Budget Task Force (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Budget Task Force - Full Report (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Albany (Box 3, Folder 18)
- SUNY Clerical Job Description (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SED Guidelines - August 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- SUNY Librarians (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Budgeting for SUNY Libraries (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Faculty Senate Committee (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Budgeting for SUNY Libraries (Box 3, Folder 24)
- SUNY Formulas (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Public Sector Labor Relations Thesaurus (1974-76), 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Public Employment Documentation Budget Sheets (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining Online Searches (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Contract J-9-M-7-0114 Account Number 515-8302 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Finance - Feinberg Papers (515-8701) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NEH 1199Drug v. Hospital Acct. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Andrew J. Biemiller - Gift for Books Acct. No. 515-8707 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Finance: Fiscal Year 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Finance: Fiscal Year 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Finance: Budget 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Finance: Budget 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Finance: Budget 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Building Proposal of NYSSILR, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR Library Supplies - General, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- NYSSILR Travel Expense Account, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Payroll Vouchers, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Payroll Vouchers, 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Payroll Vouchers, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Planning Group Questionnaire (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Mason (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Mira (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Expansion Plans (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Mason Report - Original (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Library Committee - Summer 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Space (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NYSSILR Plans (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Equipment Request - Homes and Buildings (Box 5, Folder 3)
- ILR Library - Space, Furnishings, etc. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Building - Space (Box 5, Folder 5)
- NYSSILR Library - Space Requirements (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Specification of Labor and Materials Required for Library Equipment for Classroom and Library Building (Box 5, Folder 7)
- State University Construction Fund (Box 5, Folder 8)
- B-2 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Finance - General (Pre-1975) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Catherwood Library Carrel Assignments (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Schedules - Library (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NYSSILR Library Hours (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR Library Orientation Program (Box 5, Folder 14)
- NYSSILR Course Materials - ILR 391 Spring 1959, B.G. Neas (Box 5, Folder 15)
- OCLC Catalogue (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Course Reading Material (Box 5, Folder 17)
- ILR Library - Circulation and Reserve Book Service (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Carrels (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Circulation Statistics (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Security (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Schedules and Study Space (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Circulation (Box 5, Folder 23)
- ILR Library - Schedules (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Reserve System (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Course Readings (Box 5, Folder 26)
- References Department - Library Instruction and Orientation (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Online Searching Plans - Reference (Student Use) (Box 5, Folder 28)
- OMNI-Com (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Law Materials (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Reference (Box 5, Folder 31)
- ILR Library Reference Service (Box 5, Folder 32)
- LIT Search - Fall 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Law Materials (Box 5, Folder 34)
- ILR Library - Special Projects (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Sample Handouts (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Numeric Data Files (Box 5, Folder 37)
- INF SUC Proposals (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Special Projects - Public Information Center - Correspondence, General (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Special Projects - Public Information Service (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Industrial Relations Information system Proposal (1961-) (Box 5, Folder 41)
- IRIS (Box 5, Folder 42)
- ILR Library Special Projects - IRIS-related, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- ILR Library Reference Documents (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Project Ezra (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Halfield Fund (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Telenet/Tymnet (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Online Searching 77 Budget (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Computer Search Suc. Committee (Box 5, Folder 49)
- On-Line Searching Services (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Access (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Transparencies (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Information Requests (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Dental Plans (Box 6, Folder 4)
- No-Strike Clause (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Seniority (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Cost of Living Clauses (Box 6, Folder 7)
- ILR Information Service (Box 6, Folder 8)
- ILR Library - Special Projects, Associates Program (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Associates Program (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Access - September 1977 Promotion (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Access - Prof. Staff (Box 6, Folder 12)
- NY Chamber Questionnaire (Box 6, Folder 13)
- NYSSILR - Memoranda and Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous - Information Center and Computer Proposals (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Special Projects: Public Information Service, Proposed to Dean Moore (9/1/1964) (Box 6, Folder 16)
- NYS Labor Management Information Resources Center (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Industrial Relations Information System (IRIS) (Box 6, Folder 18)
- NYSSILR - General (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Administrative Memoranda - G. Calvert (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Administrative Aide, A. Moore (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Faculty and Staff Memos (Pre-1975) (Box 6, Folder 22)
- General NYSSILR - Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 6, Folder 23)
- NYSSILR - Staff Personnel Policies Committee (Box 6, Folder 24)
- NYSSILR - Administrative Procedures (Box 6, Folder 25)
- NYSSILR - Five Year Forecast (Box 6, Folder 26)
- NYSSILR - School Dedication (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Publications - General (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Publications Distribution General (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Publications Distribution, Memos and Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Publications Distribution - Distribution Center Reports and Procedures (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Publications: Faculty Publications (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Publications: ILR Review General (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Memos (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Buffalo Extension Office (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Extension Division, Ithaca Office (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Extension Division, New York Office (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Audio-Visual Center (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Office of Resident Instruction - General (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Office of Resident Instruction, Memoranda (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Office of Resident Instruction, Reports (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Faculty Committees: Academic Integrity Code (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Faculty Committees: Committee on Academic Standard (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Faculty Committees: Committee on Accreditation (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Faculty Committees: Ad Hoc Committees (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Faculty Committees: Advisory Committee on Extension Activities (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Faculty Committees: Advisory Committee on Personnel Policy (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Associate Degree Program (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Faculty Committees: Curriculum Committee (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Faculty Committees: Committee on Distribution of Publications (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Faculty Committees: Graduate Committee (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Faculty Committees: Human Affairs Program (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Faculty Committees: Masters' Degree Program (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Faculty Committees: Nominations and Elections Committee (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Faculty Committees: Personnel Policy Committees (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Faculty Committees: Publications Distribution Comm. (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Faculty Committees: Research and Information Committee (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Faculty Committees: General (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Faculty Committees: Research and Publications Committee (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Faculty Committees: Undergraduate Programs Committee (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Faculty Memoranda: Aronson, Robert (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Faculty Memoranda: Blumen, Isadore (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Faculty Memoranda: Brooks, George (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Faculty Memoranda: Clark, M. Gardner (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Faculty Memoranda: Cook, Alice (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Faculty Memoranda: Cullen, Don (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Faculty Memoranda: Doherty, Robert (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Faculty Memoranda: Donovan, Ronald (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Faculty Memoranda: Foltman, Filician (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Faculty Memoranda: Galenson, Walter (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Administrative Memoranda: Gamm, Sara (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Faculty Memoranda: Gross, James A. (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Faculty Memoranda: Gruenfeld, L. (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Faculty Memoranda: Jenson, Vernon H. (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Faculty Memoranda: Konvitz, Milton (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Faculty Memoranda: Korman, Gerd (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Faculty Memoranda: McKelvey, Jean T. (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Faculty Memoranda: Miller, Frank (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Faculty Memoranda: Miller, J.G. (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Faculty Memoranda: Neufeld, M.F. (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Faculty Memoranda: Rehmus, Charles (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Faculty Memoranda: Risley, Robert F. (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Faculty Memoranda: Rosen, N.A. (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Faculty Memoranda: Trice, H.M. (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Faculty Memoranda: Wasmuth, W.J. (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Faculty Memoranda: Whyte, William (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Faculty Memoranda: Lawrence K. Williams (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Faculty Memoranda: Windmuller, John (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Participation Documents (Box 8, Folder 1)
- UMI (Box 8, Folder 2)
- MCA - Original Copies of Contracts (Box 8, Folder 3)
- MCA 83 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- MCA Berme (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Special Projects: General (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Risley Proposal (Box 8, Folder 7)
- NY Hoop Association (Box 8, Folder 8)
- ASPA (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Period Cataloging - USDL (Box 8, Folder 10)
- CONSER (Cataloging Project) (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Special Projects: Microfilming Corporation of America (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Special Projects: Microfilming Corporation of America, Royalties (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Contract J-9-M-8-0216, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Industrial Relations Counselors (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Labor-Industrial Relations Information Systems Barhydt - Feasibility Study (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Special Projects: Library Book Fund (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Special Projects: Library Information Program (Box 8, Folder 18)
- ILR Library - Special Projects - MCA Microfilm Publications (Box 8, Folder 19)
- LMDC Oral History - Drug and Hospital History Project (Box 8, Folder 20)
- New York City Labor Records Survey (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Come-Up (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Subject Authority File (Box 8, Folder 23)
- ILR Periodicals (Box 8, Folder 24)
- UTU Project Memoranda (Box 8, Folder 25)
- NYSSILR - International Program (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Special Projects: American Society for Personnel Administration (Box 8, Folder 27)
- NYSSILR - Special Projects "Recommended Books" Bibliography (Box 8, Folder 28)
- NYSSILR: Bibliographies on WW2 Exper. (Box 8, Folder 29)
- NYSSILR - Special Projects Bibliographical Handbook Series (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Special Projects - Elridge Collection (Box 8, Folder 31)
- NYSSILR - Special Projects, Ford Foundation Program in India (Box 8, Folder 32)
- NYSSILR - Ford Foundation Study of Retirement Policies and Practices (Box 8, Folder 33)
- NYSSILR - Special Projects Union List of Serials Project (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Special Projects - Early American History Duplicate Project (Box 8, Folder 35)
- NYSSILR - Special Projects Brochure on Library Services (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Bibliographical Survey of European Labor Organizations (Box 8, Folder 37)
- J. Gormly Miller Proposal (Box 8, Folder 38)